platformpurple.com 2015-05-02

# privacy policy | platformpurple.com

## Notice

**Platform Purple, Inc. is committed to clearly and readily disclosing its data collection practices so that you can make informed decisions about your activities in the System.**

Platform Purple, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with any third party, person or company, except as listed below.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) uses and protects any information that you give Platform Purple, Inc. when you use this web site and the platform:purple (collectively, the “System”).

Platform Purple, Inc. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our System, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Platform Purple, Inc. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are in agreement with any changes.

  * ###  Access 

Platform Purple, Inc. provides you with the opportunity to review, modify, and delete any personally identifiable information that you have previously provided. To review the information we have for you, or to have us delete any of your information, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, please contact us with the form below or by emailing techsupport@platformpurple.com. 

  * ###  Security 

Platform Purple, Inc. has taken proactive measures to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of data that it collects and stores. Platform Purple, Inc.’ network infrastructure utilizes leading technology, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software which encrypts information, to protect data at each point of transfer. Platform Purple, Inc.’ server facilities utilize up to date physical and electronic security procedures to limit access to the data so that any access is consistent with this Policy. 

  * ###  Information Collected 

So that we can provide the best possible service and improve our customer experience, Platform Purple, Inc. may collect customer details you provide us, which may include first and last name, email address, shipping and billing address, phone number and company name. Payment information is collected, where necessary, through our secure checkout process, however Platform Purple, Inc. does not store payment information. 

  * ###  Cookies 

When you visit platformpurple.com, we may send one or more cookies (small file containing characters which identify your browser). Most browsers are set to accept cookies but you can modify your browser’s settings to reject or delete cookies from some or all websites, including platformpurple.com. 

  * ###  User Communication 

If you send an email or other communication to Platform Purple, Inc., we may retain those communications and the personal information you provide in order to fulfill your request of us. We will not use return email addresses for any other use without your consent. 

  * ###  Affiliated Websites 

Platform Purple, Inc. may offer products and services in connection with third-party websites. Personally identifiable information that you provide to third-party websites may be sent to Platform Purple, Inc.. Platform Purple, Inc. processes such personally identifiable information in accordance with this Policy. The third-party websites may have different privacy practices and you should read their privacy policies before giving them your personal information. 

  * ###  Links 

Platform Purple, Inc. may present links in a format that tracks whether these links have been followed. This information is used internally to improve the quality of Platform Purple, Inc.’ products, services, and this website by tracking user trends. 

  * ###  Third-Party Websites 

This Policy only applies to this website and any other website owned and operated by Platform Purple, Inc.. Please be aware that Platform Purple, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other websites and does not exercise control over third-party websites displayed as links anywhere on this website. These third-party websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. In certain instances, if you affirmatively click through to access sponsored content or materials at sponsored websites, or affirmatively click through on a link/ad, that user’s information may be shared with the sponsor. 

  * ###  How Platform Purple, Inc. Uses Your Information 

If you purchase a product through our System, it’s possible the catalog owner from whom you purchased has requested to add your contact data to their mailing list so they can notify you about new products, special sales and/or updates to the products you purchased from them. In this case, they have promised us that it will be easy to opt out of these mailings if you wish. If you feel a catalog owner is not abiding by this policy, please contact us through the form below.

Platform Purple, Inc. may share aggregate information, such as usage and demographic data, with third parties. Aggregate information does not include personally identifiable information.

Platform Purple, Inc. reserves the right to disclose any information collected at this website if required by law or valid order of a court or other governmental authority. 

  * ###  Your California Privacy Rights 

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits those customers that are California residents to request information about how Platform Purple, Inc. discloses certain categories of personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. California residents may also request that Platform Purple, Inc. not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing use. Except as set out in this Policy, Platform Purple, Inc. does not presently share personally identifiable information with any third parties. 

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact Platform Purple, Inc. using the form below or by emailing [support@platformpurple.com](mailto:support@platformpurple.com?subject=Privacy-Policy).

Platform Purple, Inc., Inc reserves the right to update this policy without notice.

EFFECTIVE DATE July 14, 2011

privacy policy01.20.2009
